<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>CoMeT</title>
    <description>Collaborative Management of Talks: A social web system for research communities</description>
    <link>http://halley.exp.sis.pitt.edu/comet/</link>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Regulation of Intracellular Signaling via Cellular Morphology]]></title>
      <pubDate>Thursday, Jan 16 10:50 PM -0500</pubDate>
      <link>http://halley.exp.sis.pitt.edu/comet/presentColloquium.do?col_id=18696</link>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<b>Speaker:</b>&nbsp;MEGHAN DRISCOLL<br/><b>Date:</b>&nbsp;Monday, Jan 27 on 10:00 AM - 11:00 AM<br/><b>Location:</b>&nbsp;Gates Hillman Centers, ASA Conference Room 6115<br/><b>Detail:<b><p>Signaling is governed not only by the expression levels of molecules, but by their localization via mechanisms as diverse as compartmentalization in organelles, phase separation, and directed transport by motor proteins. Cell morphology likely also modulates the localization of signaling molecules, and recent advances in high-resolution light-sheet microscopy, such as lattice light-sheet microscopy, now allow imaging at the spatiotemporal resolution needed to capture the many undulations and quick dynamics of the 3D cell surface. However, these microscopes generate large datasets with detailed 3D movies that are impossible to interpret without a dedicated computational pipeline. In this seminar, I will introduce u-shape3D, a computer graphics and machine-learning pipeline to probe molecular mechanisms underlying 3D cell morphogenesis. U-shape3D includes a generic morphological motif detector that automatically finds lamellipodia, filopodia, blebs and other motifs in order to test the intriguing possibility that morphogenesis itself affects intracellular signaling.</p> <p>?</p> <p><a href="https://at.linkedin.com/in/meghan-driscoll-94691161">Meghan Driscoll</a> is finishing her postdoctoral research in Gaudenz Danuser?s lab at the University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center in Dallas. Her research focuses on investigating the function of cell morphology. As a postdoc, she developed a workflow to analyze the coupling of cell morphology with intracellular signaling. This workflow uses techniques from machine learning and computer graphics to enable analysis of high-resolution light-sheet microscopy images of cells embedded in 3D microenvironments. As a Ph.D. student in Wolfgang Losert?s lab, she studied the interaction of amoeboid cells with simple fabricated substrates, such as cliffs, ridges, and ratchets. She received a B.S. in Physics from Harvey Mudd College and a Ph.D. in Physics from the University of Maryland, College Park. She plans to establish a laboratory that will use cutting-edge approaches to investigate how 3D cell morphology governs intracellular signaling.</p> <p><em>Computational Biology</em></p> <p>For More Information, Please Contact:&nbsp;</p> <p><a href="mailto:emodoono@andrew.cmu.edu">emodoono@andrew.cmu.edu</a></p> <p>Keywords:&nbsp;</p> <p><a href="/tags/scs">SCS</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <description><![CDATA[Speaker:†MEGHAN DRISCOLLDate:†Monday, Jan 27 on 10:00 AM - 11:00 AMLocation:†Gates Hillman Centers, ASA Conference Room 6115Detail:Signaling is governed not only by the expression levels of molecules, but by their localization via mechanisms as diverse as compartmentalization in organelles, phase separation, and directed transport by motor proteins. Cell morphology likely also modulates the localization of signaling molecules, and recent advances in high-resolution light-sheet microscopy, such as lattice light-sheet microscopy, now allow imaging at the spatiotemporal resolution needed to capture the many undulations and quick dynamics of the 3D cell surface. However, these microscopes generate large datasets with detailed 3D movies that are impossible to interpret without a dedicated computational pipeline. In this seminar, I will introduce u-shape3D, a computer graphics and machine-learning pipeline to probe molecular mechanisms underlying 3D cell morphogenesis. U-shape3D includes a generic morphological motif detector that automatically finds lamellipodia, filopodia, blebs and other motifs in order to test the intriguing possibility that morphogenesis itself affects intracellular signaling. ? Meghan Driscoll is finishing her postdoctoral research in Gaudenz Danuser?s lab at the University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center in Dallas. Her research focuses on investigating the function of cell morphology. As a postdoc, she developed a workflow to analyze the coupling of cell morphology with intracellular signaling. This workflow uses techniques from machine learning and computer graphics to enable analysis of high-resolution light-sheet microscopy images of cells embedded in 3D microenvironments. As a Ph.D. student in Wolfgang Losert?s lab, she studied the interaction of amoeboid cells with simple fabricated substrates, such as cliffs, ridges, and ratchets. She received a B.S. in Physics from Harvey Mudd College and a Ph.D. in Physics from the University of Maryland, College Park. She plans to establish a laboratory that will use cutting-edge approaches to investigate how 3D cell morphology governs intracellular signaling. Computational Biology For More Information, Please Contact:† emodoono@andrew.cmu.edu Keywords:† SCS]]></description>
      <author>comet.paws</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Regulation of healthy aging]]></title>
      <pubDate>Thursday, Dec 12 10:02 PM -0500</pubDate>
      <link>http://halley.exp.sis.pitt.edu/comet/presentColloquium.do?col_id=18606</link>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<b>Speaker:</b>&nbsp;Heidi Tissenbaum<br/><b>Date:</b>&nbsp;Monday, Jan 27 on 11:00 AM - 12:00 AM<br/><b>Location:</b>&nbsp;219B Langley Hall <br/><b>Detail:<b><p>What is the signature for healthy aging? I will discuss our work to define a molecular and genetic signature for healthy aging. Most recently, our work has focused on the effect of a high sugar diet on&nbsp;<em>C. elegans.&nbsp;</em>&nbsp;My talk will outline our results dissecting the effect of a high sugar diet in the context of a whole organism examining alterations in diet, stress response, and aging.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <description><![CDATA[Speaker:†Heidi TissenbaumDate:†Monday, Jan 27 on 11:00 AM - 12:00 AMLocation:†219B Langley Hall Detail:What is the signature for healthy aging? I will discuss our work to define a molecular and genetic signature for healthy aging. Most recently, our work has focused on the effect of a high sugar diet on†C. elegans.††My talk will outline our results dissecting the effect of a high sugar diet in the context of a whole organism examining alterations in diet, stress response, and aging.]]></description>
      <author>lisun</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Hormone-Dependent Neurocircuits Optimize Activity and Skeletal Health in Females]]></title>
      <pubDate>Monday, Jan 06 4:40 PM -0500</pubDate>
      <link>http://halley.exp.sis.pitt.edu/comet/presentColloquium.do?col_id=18625</link>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<b>Speaker:</b>&nbsp;Holly Ingraham<br/><b>Date:</b>&nbsp;Monday, Jan 27 on 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM<br/><b>Location:</b>&nbsp;Online - Webinar<br/><b>Detail:<b><p>NIH Neuroscience Series Seminar<br /> For more information go to <a href="https://neuroscience.nih.gov/neuroseries">https://neuroscience.nih.gov/neuroseries</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <description><![CDATA[Speaker:†Holly IngrahamDate:†Monday, Jan 27 on 12:00 PM - 1:00 PMLocation:†Online - WebinarDetail:NIH Neuroscience Series Seminar For more information go to https://neuroscience.nih.gov/neuroseries]]></description>
      <author>comet.paws</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Gotta have HeART: Improving Storage Efficiency by Exploiting Disk-reliability Heterogeneity]]></title>
      <pubDate>Thursday, Jan 16 10:48 PM -0500</pubDate>
      <link>http://halley.exp.sis.pitt.edu/comet/presentColloquium.do?col_id=18692</link>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<b>Speaker:</b>&nbsp;SAURABH KADEKODI<br/><b>Date:</b>&nbsp;Monday, Jan 27 on 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM<br/><b>Location:</b>&nbsp;Gates Hillman Centers, Traffic21 Classroom 6501<br/><b>Detail:<b><h2>Gotta have HeART: Improving Storage Efficiency by Exploiting Disk-reliability Heterogeneity</h2> <p>Large-scale cluster storage systems typically consist of a heterogeneous mix of storage devices with significantly varying failure rates. Despite such differences among devices, redundancy settings are generally configured in a one-scheme-for-all fashion. In this paper, we make a case for exploiting reliability heterogeneity to tailor redundancy settings to different device groups. We present HeART, an online tuning tool that guides selection of, and transitions between redundancy settings for long-term data reliability, based on observed reliability properties of each disk group. By processing disk failure data over time, HeART identifies the boundaries and steady-state failure rate for each deployed disk group (e.g., by make/model). Using this information, HeART suggests the most space-efficient redundancy option allowed that will achieve the specified target data reliability with much fewer disks than one-scheme-for-all approaches.<br /> <br /> <em>Presented in Partial Fulfillment of the CSD Speaking Skills Requirement.</em></p> <p><a href="http://www.cs.cmu.edu/afs/.cs.cmu.edu/Web/Posters/CSSpeakingSkills-SKadekodi20.pdf" target="_blank">Poster</a></p> <p>For More Information, Please Contact:&nbsp;</p> <p><a href="mailto:deb@cs.cmu.edu">deb@cs.cmu.edu</a></p> <p>Keywords:&nbsp;</p> <p><a href="/tags/csd">CSD</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <description><![CDATA[Speaker:†SAURABH KADEKODIDate:†Monday, Jan 27 on 12:00 PM - 1:00 PMLocation:†Gates Hillman Centers, Traffic21 Classroom 6501Detail:Gotta have HeART: Improving Storage Efficiency by Exploiting Disk-reliability Heterogeneity Large-scale cluster storage systems typically consist of a heterogeneous mix of storage devices with significantly varying failure rates. Despite such differences among devices, redundancy settings are generally configured in a one-scheme-for-all fashion. In this paper, we make a case for exploiting reliability heterogeneity to tailor redundancy settings to different device groups. We present HeART, an online tuning tool that guides selection of, and transitions between redundancy settings for long-term data reliability, based on observed reliability properties of each disk group. By processing disk failure data over time, HeART identifies the boundaries and steady-state failure rate for each deployed disk group (e.g., by make/model). Using this information, HeART suggests the most space-efficient redundancy option allowed that will achieve the specified target data reliability with much fewer disks than one-scheme-for-all approaches. Presented in Partial Fulfillment of the CSD Speaking Skills Requirement. Poster For More Information, Please Contact:† deb@cs.cmu.edu Keywords:† CSD]]></description>
      <author>comet.paws</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Self-Persuasion: Evidence from Field Experiments at Two International Debating Competitions]]></title>
      <pubDate>Monday, Jan 20 2:15 PM -0500</pubDate>
      <link>http://halley.exp.sis.pitt.edu/comet/presentColloquium.do?col_id=18710</link>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<b>Speaker:</b>&nbsp;Egon Tripodi<br/><b>Date:</b>&nbsp;Monday, Jan 27 on 12:00 PM - 1:15 PM<br/><b>Location:</b>&nbsp;Porter Hall 223D<br/><b>Detail:<b><p>Does the wish to convince others lead people to persuade themselves about the moral and factual superiority of their position? We investigate this question in the context of two international debating competitions, where persuasion goals (pro<br /> or contra a motion) are randomly assigned to debaters shortly before the debate. Using incentives for truthful reporting, we find evidence of self-persuasion in the form of (i) factual beliefs that become more conveniently aligned with the debater?s side of the motion, (ii) shifts in attitudes, reflected in an increased willingness to donate to goal-aligned charities, and (iii) higher confidence in the strength of one?s position in the debate. Self-persuasion occurs before the debate and subsequent<br /> participation in the open exchange of arguments does not lead to convergence in beliefs and attitudes. Our results lend support to interactionist theories of cognition and suggest that the desire to persuade is an important driver of opinion formation and political partisanship.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <description><![CDATA[Speaker:†Egon TripodiDate:†Monday, Jan 27 on 12:00 PM - 1:15 PMLocation:†Porter Hall 223DDetail:Does the wish to convince others lead people to persuade themselves about the moral and factual superiority of their position? We investigate this question in the context of two international debating competitions, where persuasion goals (pro or contra a motion) are randomly assigned to debaters shortly before the debate. Using incentives for truthful reporting, we find evidence of self-persuasion in the form of (i) factual beliefs that become more conveniently aligned with the debater?s side of the motion, (ii) shifts in attitudes, reflected in an increased willingness to donate to goal-aligned charities, and (iii) higher confidence in the strength of one?s position in the debate. Self-persuasion occurs before the debate and subsequent participation in the open exchange of arguments does not lead to convergence in beliefs and attitudes. Our results lend support to interactionist theories of cognition and suggest that the desire to persuade is an important driver of opinion formation and political partisanship.]]></description>
      <author>comet.paws</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Does Workplace Competition Increase Labor Supply? Evidence from a Field Experiment]]></title>
      <pubDate>Tuesday, Jan 07 11:28 AM -0500</pubDate>
      <link>http://halley.exp.sis.pitt.edu/comet/presentColloquium.do?col_id=18645</link>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<b>Speaker:</b>&nbsp;Amalia Miller<br/><b>Date:</b>&nbsp;Monday, Jan 27 on 12:00 PM - 1:20 PM<br/><b>Location:</b>&nbsp;Hamburg Hall 1002<br/><b>Detail:<b><p>This paper develops a novel field experiment to test the implicit prediction of tournament theory that competition increases work time and can therefore contribute to the long work hours required in elite occupations. A majority of workers in the treatment without explicit financial incentives worked past the minimum time, but awarding a tournament prize increased work time and effort by over 80% and lowered costs of effort or output by over a third. Effort was similar with alternative (piece rate, low-prize tournament) bonuses. Men worked longer than women in the high-prize tournament, but for the same duration in other treatments.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <description><![CDATA[Speaker:†Amalia MillerDate:†Monday, Jan 27 on 12:00 PM - 1:20 PMLocation:†Hamburg Hall 1002Detail:This paper develops a novel field experiment to test the implicit prediction of tournament theory that competition increases work time and can therefore contribute to the long work hours required in elite occupations. A majority of workers in the treatment without explicit financial incentives worked past the minimum time, but awarding a tournament prize increased work time and effort by over 80% and lowered costs of effort or output by over a third. Effort was similar with alternative (piece rate, low-prize tournament) bonuses. Men worked longer than women in the high-prize tournament, but for the same duration in other treatments.]]></description>
      <author>comet.paws</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Dissertation Defense: Exploring C-H Functionalization Reactions with Theory and Experiment]]></title>
      <pubDate>Thursday, Jan 16 10:48 PM -0500</pubDate>
      <link>http://halley.exp.sis.pitt.edu/comet/presentColloquium.do?col_id=18693</link>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<b>Speaker:</b>&nbsp;Humair Omer<br/><b>Date:</b>&nbsp;Monday, Jan 27 on 12:30 PM - 1:30 PM<br/><b>Location:</b>&nbsp;Eberly Hall, 307<br/><b>Detail:<b><p>Chemistry PhD Defense:&nbsp; Exploring C?H Functionalization Reactions with Theory and Experiment</p> <p>Advisors:&nbsp;&nbsp;Kay Brummond and Peng Liu</p> <p>Committee members:&nbsp;</p> <ul> <li>Kenneth Jordan</li> <li>Paul Floreancig</li> <li>Kevin Noonan (Department of Chemical and Petroleum Engineering, University of PittsburghChemistry, Carnegie Mellon University)</li> </ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <description><![CDATA[Speaker:†Humair OmerDate:†Monday, Jan 27 on 12:30 PM - 1:30 PMLocation:†Eberly Hall, 307Detail:Chemistry PhD Defense:† Exploring C?H Functionalization Reactions with Theory and Experiment Advisors:††Kay Brummond and Peng Liu Committee members:† Kenneth Jordan Paul Floreancig Kevin Noonan (Department of Chemical and Petroleum Engineering, University of PittsburghChemistry, Carnegie Mellon University)]]></description>
      <author>comet.paws</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Reconstructing 3D Human Avatars from Monocular Images]]></title>
      <pubDate>Monday, Jan 20 2:19 PM -0500</pubDate>
      <link>http://halley.exp.sis.pitt.edu/comet/presentColloquium.do?col_id=18715</link>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<b>Speaker:</b>&nbsp;THIEMO ALLDIECK<br/><b>Date:</b>&nbsp;Monday, Jan 27 on 3:00 PM - 4:00 PM<br/><b>Location:</b>&nbsp;Gates Hillman Centers, Traffic21 Classroom 6501<br/><b>Detail:<b><p>Statistical 3D human body models have helped us to better understand human shape and motion and already enabled exciting new applications. However, if we want to learn detailed, personalized, and clothed models of human shape, motion, and dynamics, we require new approaches that learn from ubiquitous data such as plain RGB-images and video. I will discuss recent advances in personalized body shape and clothing estimation from monocular video, from a few frames, and even from a single image. We developed effective methods to learn detailed avatars without the need for expensive scanning equipment. These methods are easy to use and enable personalized avatar creation for example for VR and AR applications. I will conclude my talk by outlining the next challenges in human shape reconstruction.</p> <p><a href="http://https://graphics.tu-bs.de/people/alldieck">Thiemo Alldieck</a> obtained his Master?s degree from Aalborg University (Denmark) in Vision, Graphics and Interactive Systems in 2015. Since 2016 he is a Ph.D. student at the Computer Graphics Lab at TU Braunschweig (Germany). Currently, he is a research intern at Facebook Reality Labs, Pittsburgh. In 2018 he was a visiting Ph.D. in the Real Virtual Humans and Graphics Vision &amp; Video groups at Max-Planck Institute for Informatics, Saarbr&uuml;cken (Germany). He works in on-going close cooperation with the groups on the topic of monocular human shape reconstruction. His work has been published in various computer vision conferences including CVPR, ICCV, and 3DV.</p> <p><em>The VASC seminar is supported in part by Facebook Reality Labs Pittsburgh</em></p> <p><a href="http://www.cs.cmu.edu/afs/.cs.cmu.edu/Web/Posters/VASC-TAlldieck20.pdf" target="_blank">Poster</a></p> <p><a href="https://www.ri.cmu.edu/event/reconstructing-3d-human-avatars-from-monocular-images/">Event Website</a></p> <p>For More Information, Please Contact:&nbsp;</p> <p><a href="mailto:cdowney@andrew.cmu.edu">cdowney@andrew.cmu.edu</a></p> <p>Keywords:&nbsp;</p> <p><a href="/tags/ri-vasc">RI / VASC</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <description><![CDATA[Speaker:†THIEMO ALLDIECKDate:†Monday, Jan 27 on 3:00 PM - 4:00 PMLocation:†Gates Hillman Centers, Traffic21 Classroom 6501Detail:Statistical 3D human body models have helped us to better understand human shape and motion and already enabled exciting new applications. However, if we want to learn detailed, personalized, and clothed models of human shape, motion, and dynamics, we require new approaches that learn from ubiquitous data such as plain RGB-images and video. I will discuss recent advances in personalized body shape and clothing estimation from monocular video, from a few frames, and even from a single image. We developed effective methods to learn detailed avatars without the need for expensive scanning equipment. These methods are easy to use and enable personalized avatar creation for example for VR and AR applications. I will conclude my talk by outlining the next challenges in human shape reconstruction. Thiemo Alldieck obtained his Master?s degree from Aalborg University (Denmark) in Vision, Graphics and Interactive Systems in 2015. Since 2016 he is a Ph.D. student at the Computer Graphics Lab at TU Braunschweig (Germany). Currently, he is a research intern at Facebook Reality Labs, Pittsburgh. In 2018 he was a visiting Ph.D. in the Real Virtual Humans and Graphics Vision & Video groups at Max-Planck Institute for Informatics, Saarbr¸cken (Germany). He works in on-going close cooperation with the groups on the topic of monocular human shape reconstruction. His work has been published in various computer vision conferences including CVPR, ICCV, and 3DV. The VASC seminar is supported in part by Facebook Reality Labs Pittsburgh Poster Event Website For More Information, Please Contact:† cdowney@andrew.cmu.edu Keywords:† RI / VASC]]></description>
      <author>comet.paws</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Geo-usage analysis and modeling of bike sharing system at hilly cities]]></title>
      <pubDate>Wednesday, Jan 22 9:05 PM -0500</pubDate>
      <link>http://halley.exp.sis.pitt.edu/comet/presentColloquium.do?col_id=18766</link>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<b>Speaker:</b>&nbsp;Injung Kim<br/><b>Date:</b>&nbsp;Monday, Jan 27 on 3:00 PM - 4:00 PM<br/><b>Location:</b>&nbsp;5317 Seminar Hall<br/><b>Detail:<b><p>&nbsp;</p> <p class="MsoNormal" style="mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:auto">Today, 55% of the world&#39;s population lives in urban area, and a proportion that is expected to increase to 68% by 2050.</p> <p class="MsoNormal" style="mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:auto">Cities all over the world struggling to maintain cost effective and sustainable transport system, and bike sharing emerges as a solution.</p> <p class="MsoNormal" style="mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:auto">A bike-sharing system or bicycle-sharing system offers a self-service, short-term, one-way urban bicycle rental in public spaces,</p> <p class="MsoNormal" style="mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:auto">for several target groups and with network characteristics. Most BSS research is about re-balancing and predict usage or so,</p> <p class="MsoNormal" style="mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:auto">however we focus on the usability pattern in the hilly cities. Here we statistically analyze the BSS usage pattern in the hilly city</p> <p class="MsoNormal" style="mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:auto">and predict its future pattern with our modelling. By doing this, we will also build the system to give some credits to the people</p> <p class="MsoNormal" style="mso-margin-top-alt:auto;mso-margin-bottom-alt:auto">who can return the bike at the hilly station or so and it will eventually reduce the cost of re-balancing.</p> <p> <style type="text/css"><!-- /* Font Definitions */ @font-face {font-family:"Cambria Math"; panose-1:2 4 5 3 5 4 6 3 2 4; mso-font-charset:0; mso-generic-font-family:roman; mso-font-pitch:variable; mso-font-signature:3 0 0 0 1 0;} @font-face {font-family:Calibri; panose-1:2 15 5 2 2 2 4 3 2 4; mso-font-charset:0; mso-generic-font-family:swiss; mso-font-pitch:variable; mso-font-signature:-469750017 -1073732485 9 0 511 0;} /* Style Definitions */ p.MsoNormal, li.MsoNormal, div.MsoNormal {mso-style-unhide:no; mso-style-qformat:yes; mso-style-parent:""; margin:0in; margin-bottom:.0001pt; mso-pagination:widow-orphan; font-size:11.0pt; font-family:"Calibri",sans-serif; mso-ascii-font-family:Calibri; mso-ascii-theme-font:minor-latin; mso-fareast-font-family:"Times New Roman"; mso-fareast-theme-font:minor-fareast; mso-hansi-font-family:Calibri; mso-hansi-theme-font:minor-latin; mso-bidi-font-family:"Times New Roman"; mso-bidi-theme-font:minor-bidi;} .MsoChpDefault {mso-style-type:export-only; mso-default-props:yes; font-family:"Calibri",sans-serif; mso-ascii-font-family:Calibri; mso-ascii-theme-font:minor-latin; mso-fareast-font-family:"Times New Roman"; mso-fareast-theme-font:minor-fareast; mso-hansi-font-family:Calibri; mso-hansi-theme-font:minor-latin; mso-bidi-font-family:"Times New Roman"; mso-bidi-theme-font:minor-bidi;}size:8.5in 11.0in; margin:1.0in 1.0in 1.0in 1.0in; mso-header-margin:.5in; mso-footer-margin:.5in; mso-paper-source:0;} div.WordSection1 {page:WordSection1;}</style><style class="darkreader darkreader--sync" media="screen"> </style> </p>]]></content:encoded>
      <description><![CDATA[Speaker:†Injung KimDate:†Monday, Jan 27 on 3:00 PM - 4:00 PMLocation:†5317 Seminar HallDetail:† Today, 55% of the world's population lives in urban area, and a proportion that is expected to increase to 68% by 2050. Cities all over the world struggling to maintain cost effective and sustainable transport system, and bike sharing emerges as a solution. A bike-sharing system or bicycle-sharing system offers a self-service, short-term, one-way urban bicycle rental in public spaces, for several target groups and with network characteristics. Most BSS research is about re-balancing and predict usage or so, however we focus on the usability pattern in the hilly cities. Here we statistically analyze the BSS usage pattern in the hilly city and predict its future pattern with our modelling. By doing this, we will also build the system to give some credits to the people who can return the bike at the hilly station or so and it will eventually reduce the cost of re-balancing. /* Font Definitions */ @font-face {font-family:"Cambria Math"; panose-1:2 4 5 3 5 4 6 3 2 4; mso-font-charset:0; mso-generic-font-family:roman; mso-font-pitch:variable; mso-font-signature:3 0 0 0 1 0;} @font-face {font-family:Calibri; panose-1:2 15 5 2 2 2 4 3 2 4; mso-font-charset:0; mso-generic-font-family:swiss; mso-font-pitch:variable; mso-font-signature:-469750017 -1073732485 9 0 511 0;} /* Style Definitions */ p.MsoNormal, li.MsoNormal, div.MsoNormal {mso-style-unhide:no; mso-style-qformat:yes; mso-style-parent:""; margin:0in; margin-bottom:.0001pt; mso-pagination:widow-orphan; font-size:11.0pt; font-family:"Calibri",sans-serif; mso-ascii-font-family:Calibri; mso-ascii-theme-font:minor-latin; mso-fareast-font-family:"Times New Roman"; mso-fareast-theme-font:minor-fareast; mso-hansi-font-family:Calibri; mso-hansi-theme-font:minor-latin; mso-bidi-font-family:"Times New Roman"; mso-bidi-theme-font:minor-bidi;} .MsoChpDefault {mso-style-type:export-only; mso-default-props:yes; font-family:"Calibri",sans-serif; mso-ascii-font-family:Calibri; mso-ascii-theme-font:minor-latin; mso-fareast-font-family:"Times New Roman"; mso-fareast-theme-font:minor-fareast; mso-hansi-font-family:Calibri; mso-hansi-theme-font:minor-latin; mso-bidi-font-family:"Times New Roman"; mso-bidi-theme-font:minor-bidi;}size:8.5in 11.0in; margin:1.0in 1.0in 1.0in 1.0in; mso-header-margin:.5in; mso-footer-margin:.5in; mso-paper-source:0;} div.WordSection1 {page:WordSection1;}]]></description>
      <author>Arun Balajiee</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Vision and Autonomous Systems Seminar]]></title>
      <pubDate>Monday, Jan 27 4:28 PM -0500</pubDate>
      <link>http://halley.exp.sis.pitt.edu/comet/presentColloquium.do?col_id=18779</link>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<b>Speaker:</b>&nbsp;THIEMO ALLDIECK<br/><b>Date:</b>&nbsp;Monday, Jan 27 on 3:00 PM - 4:00 PM<br/><b>Location:</b>&nbsp;Gates Hillman Centers Traffic21 Classroom 6501<br/><b>Detail:<b><p>Statistical 3D human body models have helped us to better understand human shape and motion and already enabled exciting new applications. However, if we want to learn detailed, personalized, and clothed models of human shape, motion, and dynamics, we require new approaches that learn from ubiquitous data such as plain RGB-images and video. I will discuss recent advances in personalized body shape and clothing estimation from monocular video, from a few frames, and even from a single image. We developed effective methods to learn detailed avatars without the need for expensive scanning equipment. These methods are easy to use and enable personalized avatar creation for example for VR and AR applications. I will conclude my talk by outlining the next challenges in human shape reconstruction.</p> <p>&mdash;</p> <p><a href="http://https//graphics.tu-bs.de/people/alldieck">Thiemo Alldieck</a>&nbsp;obtained his Master&rsquo;s degree from Aalborg University (Denmark) in Vision, Graphics and Interactive Systems in 2015. Since 2016 he is a Ph.D. student at the Computer Graphics Lab at TU Braunschweig (Germany). Currently, he is a research intern at Facebook Reality Labs, Pittsburgh. In 2018 he was a visiting Ph.D. in the Real Virtual Humans and Graphics Vision &amp; Video groups at Max-Planck Institute for Informatics, Saarbr&uuml;cken (Germany). He works in on-going close cooperation with the groups on the topic of monocular human shape reconstruction. His work has been published in various computer vision conferences including CVPR, ICCV, and 3DV.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <description><![CDATA[Speaker:†THIEMO ALLDIECKDate:†Monday, Jan 27 on 3:00 PM - 4:00 PMLocation:†Gates Hillman Centers Traffic21 Classroom 6501Detail:Statistical 3D human body models have helped us to better understand human shape and motion and already enabled exciting new applications. However, if we want to learn detailed, personalized, and clothed models of human shape, motion, and dynamics, we require new approaches that learn from ubiquitous data such as plain RGB-images and video. I will discuss recent advances in personalized body shape and clothing estimation from monocular video, from a few frames, and even from a single image. We developed effective methods to learn detailed avatars without the need for expensive scanning equipment. These methods are easy to use and enable personalized avatar creation for example for VR and AR applications. I will conclude my talk by outlining the next challenges in human shape reconstruction. ? Thiemo Alldieck†obtained his Master?s degree from Aalborg University (Denmark) in Vision, Graphics and Interactive Systems in 2015. Since 2016 he is a Ph.D. student at the Computer Graphics Lab at TU Braunschweig (Germany). Currently, he is a research intern at Facebook Reality Labs, Pittsburgh. In 2018 he was a visiting Ph.D. in the Real Virtual Humans and Graphics Vision & Video groups at Max-Planck Institute for Informatics, Saarbr¸cken (Germany). He works in on-going close cooperation with the groups on the topic of monocular human shape reconstruction. His work has been published in various computer vision conferences including CVPR, ICCV, and 3DV.]]></description>
      <author>yanwuxu</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Who's Using Your Data? Data Privacy Panel & Dinner]]></title>
      <pubDate>Monday, Jan 20 2:25 PM -0500</pubDate>
      <link>http://halley.exp.sis.pitt.edu/comet/presentColloquium.do?col_id=18716</link>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<b>Speaker:</b>&nbsp;LISA MARTINELLI<br/><b>Date:</b>&nbsp;Monday, Jan 27 on 4:00 PM - 8:00 PM<br/><b>Location:</b>&nbsp;Alumni Hall, Connolly Ballroom<br/><b>Detail:<b><p>How is your personal information is being used, collected, and shared? Who is profiting from it? Discover the debates happening behind-the-scenes about your data, and how you can protect your details.&nbsp;</p> <ul> <li>4-6 p.m. - Resource fair with details about how to keep your data private and cybersecurity research at Pitt.&nbsp;</li> <li>6 p.m. - Buffet dinner &amp; panel discussion</li> </ul> <p><br /> <strong>&raquo; RSVP:&nbsp;<a href="http://pi.tt/privacy">pi.tt/privacy</a></strong></p> <p><br /> Featuring:</p> <ul> <li>Lisa Martinelli, Vice President and Chief Privacy Officer of Highmark Health</li> <li>David Hickton, founding director of the University of Pittsburgh Institute for Cyber Law, Policy, and Security</li> <li>Joel Garman, University of Pittsburgh&#39;s Chief Information Security Officer</li> <li>Nathan Urban, Vice Provost for Graduate Studies and Strategic Initiatives.</li> </ul>]]></content:encoded>
      <description><![CDATA[Speaker:†LISA MARTINELLIDate:†Monday, Jan 27 on 4:00 PM - 8:00 PMLocation:†Alumni Hall, Connolly BallroomDetail:How is your personal information is being used, collected, and shared? Who is profiting from it? Discover the debates happening behind-the-scenes about your data, and how you can protect your details.† 4-6 p.m. - Resource fair with details about how to keep your data private and cybersecurity research at Pitt.† 6 p.m. - Buffet dinner & panel discussion ª RSVP:†pi.tt/privacy Featuring: Lisa Martinelli, Vice President and Chief Privacy Officer of Highmark Health David Hickton, founding director of the University of Pittsburgh Institute for Cyber Law, Policy, and Security Joel Garman, University of Pittsburgh's Chief Information Security Officer Nathan Urban, Vice Provost for Graduate Studies and Strategic Initiatives.]]></description>
      <author>comet.paws</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Reporting Peers' Wrongdoing: Experimental Evidence on the Effect of Financial Incentives on Morally Controversial Behavior]]></title>
      <pubDate>Monday, Jan 20 2:18 PM -0500</pubDate>
      <link>http://halley.exp.sis.pitt.edu/comet/presentColloquium.do?col_id=18713</link>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<b>Speaker:</b>&nbsp;Stefano Fiorin<br/><b>Date:</b>&nbsp;Tuesday, Jan 28 on 9:00 AM - 10:15 AM<br/><b>Location:</b>&nbsp;Porter Hall 223D<br/><b>Detail:<b><p>I study how moral concerns influence the efficacy of financial incentives. I analyze a morally<br /> ambiguous behavior: the reporting of peers? wrongdoing. Peers often know more than principals<br /> about agents. However, denouncing a peer to an authority is morally controversial, as it might<br /> prevent future misconduct but also harm the peer. Denunciations are sometimes encouraged through financial rewards. Yet, incentives could backfire if being paid for harming others is felt as morally unacceptable. I run a field experiment with employees of the Afghan Ministry of Education, who are asked to confidentially report on their colleagues? attendance. I use a two-by-two design. To estimate the effect of rewards on denunciations, I randomize whether or not reports are incentivized. To explore the role of moral considerations, I also cross-randomize the perceived consequentiality of the reports. In the first group, employees are given examples of the penalties that might be imposed on absentees. Without rewards, 15% of these participants issue reports of recent absence that they believe can have negative consequences for their colleagues. Only 10% of employees report when denunciations are incentivized. In the second group, participants are instead guaranteed that their reports will not be forwarded to the government.<br /> Knowing that reporting is inconsequential, without rewards, 6% of employees denounce absence. Incentives do not backfire when moral concerns are limited through the guarantee that denunciations will not lead to any penalty for their peers (the incentivized reporting rate is 12%). Additionally, employees who are absent according to alternative sources are more likely to be reported. Treatment conditions do not affect the accuracy of the reports. Overall, results suggest that employees report because they share the government?s objective to reduce absence, but are morally averse to being paid for harming their peers.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <description><![CDATA[Speaker:†Stefano FiorinDate:†Tuesday, Jan 28 on 9:00 AM - 10:15 AMLocation:†Porter Hall 223DDetail:I study how moral concerns influence the efficacy of financial incentives. I analyze a morally ambiguous behavior: the reporting of peers? wrongdoing. Peers often know more than principals about agents. However, denouncing a peer to an authority is morally controversial, as it might prevent future misconduct but also harm the peer. Denunciations are sometimes encouraged through financial rewards. Yet, incentives could backfire if being paid for harming others is felt as morally unacceptable. I run a field experiment with employees of the Afghan Ministry of Education, who are asked to confidentially report on their colleagues? attendance. I use a two-by-two design. To estimate the effect of rewards on denunciations, I randomize whether or not reports are incentivized. To explore the role of moral considerations, I also cross-randomize the perceived consequentiality of the reports. In the first group, employees are given examples of the penalties that might be imposed on absentees. Without rewards, 15% of these participants issue reports of recent absence that they believe can have negative consequences for their colleagues. Only 10% of employees report when denunciations are incentivized. In the second group, participants are instead guaranteed that their reports will not be forwarded to the government. Knowing that reporting is inconsequential, without rewards, 6% of employees denounce absence. Incentives do not backfire when moral concerns are limited through the guarantee that denunciations will not lead to any penalty for their peers (the incentivized reporting rate is 12%). Additionally, employees who are absent according to alternative sources are more likely to be reported. Treatment conditions do not affect the accuracy of the reports. Overall, results suggest that employees report because they share the government?s objective to reduce absence, but are morally averse to being paid for harming their peers.]]></description>
      <author>comet.paws</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Social Media in the Age of Misinformation, Part 2]]></title>
      <pubDate>Sunday, Jan 26 10:46 AM -0500</pubDate>
      <link>http://halley.exp.sis.pitt.edu/comet/presentColloquium.do?col_id=18745</link>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<b>Speaker:</b>&nbsp;An Xiao Mina<br/><b>Date:</b>&nbsp;Tuesday, Jan 28 on 11:00 AM - 12:00 PM<br/><b>Location:</b>&nbsp;Online - Webinar<br/><b>Detail:<b><p>Join technologist and digital media scholar An Xiao Mina for a global exploration of internet memes as agents of pop culture, politics, protest, and propaganda on- and offline. Based on her new book, Memes to Movements: How the World&rsquo;s Most Viral Mediais Changing Social Protest and Power (Beacon Press, January 2019), Mina uses social media-driven movements to unpack the mechanics of memes and how they operate to reinforce, amplify, and shape today&rsquo;s politics.</p> <h1>Presenters</h1> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p><img src="https://gallery.mailchimp.com/de58424ef2e609298efbb4a00/images/f6e3ff76-cba1-4d43-a8c3-c6a3276d230d.jpg" style="float:left; height:133px; margin:0px; width:100px" /><br /> An Xiao Mina is author of Memes to Movements: How the World&rsquo;s Most Viral Media is Changing Social Protest and Power. She leads the product team at Meedan, where they are building Check, a platform for collaboratively verifying news in real time, and Bridge, a platform for translating social media and messaging app content. She is also a co-founder at the Credibility Coalition, an effort to develop a standard for assessing content credibility online, and co-chair of the W3C Credible Web Community Group</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <description><![CDATA[Speaker:†An Xiao MinaDate:†Tuesday, Jan 28 on 11:00 AM - 12:00 PMLocation:†Online - WebinarDetail:Join technologist and digital media scholar An Xiao Mina for a global exploration of internet memes as agents of pop culture, politics, protest, and propaganda on- and offline. Based on her new book, Memes to Movements: How the World?s Most Viral Mediais Changing Social Protest and Power (Beacon Press, January 2019), Mina uses social media-driven movements to unpack the mechanics of memes and how they operate to reinforce, amplify, and shape today?s politics. Presenters † An Xiao Mina is author of Memes to Movements: How the World?s Most Viral Media is Changing Social Protest and Power. She leads the product team at Meedan, where they are building Check, a platform for collaboratively verifying news in real time, and Bridge, a platform for translating social media and messaging app content. She is also a co-founder at the Credibility Coalition, an effort to develop a standard for assessing content credibility online, and co-chair of the W3C Credible Web Community Group]]></description>
      <author>comet.paws</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[lterations in circadian machinery and ?-oxidation of fatty acids in the pathogenesis of alcohol-induced liver injury]]></title>
      <pubDate>Monday, Jan 20 2:18 PM -0500</pubDate>
      <link>http://halley.exp.sis.pitt.edu/comet/presentColloquium.do?col_id=18714</link>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<b>Speaker:</b>&nbsp;Dr. Suthat Liangpunsakul<br/><b>Date:</b>&nbsp;Tuesday, Jan 28 on 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM<br/><b>Location:</b>&nbsp;Biomedical Science Tower 1, S123<br/><b>Detail:<b><p>As part of the <a href="http://www.livercenter.pitt.edu/seminars">PLRC Seminar series</a>,&nbsp; Dr. Suthat Liangpunsakul, Professor of Medicine at Indiana University School of Medicine, will present on &quot;Alterations in circadian machinery and ?-oxidation of fatty acids in the pathogenesis of alcohol-induced liver injury .&quot;</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <description><![CDATA[Speaker:†Dr. Suthat LiangpunsakulDate:†Tuesday, Jan 28 on 12:00 PM - 1:00 PMLocation:†Biomedical Science Tower 1, S123Detail:As part of the PLRC Seminar series,† Dr. Suthat Liangpunsakul, Professor of Medicine at Indiana University School of Medicine, will present on "Alterations in circadian machinery and ?-oxidation of fatty acids in the pathogenesis of alcohol-induced liver injury ."]]></description>
      <author>comet.paws</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Tax, Business and Accounting Issues for Startups*]]></title>
      <pubDate>Wednesday, Jan 01 6:29 PM -0500</pubDate>
      <link>http://halley.exp.sis.pitt.edu/comet/presentColloquium.do?col_id=18620</link>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<b>Speaker:</b>&nbsp;William Richardson<br/><b>Date:</b>&nbsp;Tuesday, Jan 28 on 12:30 PM - 2:00 PM<br/><b>Location:</b>&nbsp;Swartz Center for Entrepreneurship, Tepper Quad<br/><b>Detail:<b><h2>Tax, Business and Accounting Issues for Startups*</h2> <p><strong>Tuesday, January 28, 2020?</strong><br /> 12:30 p.m. ? 2:00 p.m.?<br /> Swartz Center for Entrepreneurship, Tepper Quad<br /> ?Presenter: <a href="https://www.sisterson.com/william-richardson" target="_blank">William Richardson</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/carissajosephcpa/" target="_blank">Carissa Habsburg</a> &amp; <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/megan-e-rechenberg-cpa-35b1b341/" target="_blank">Megan Rechenberg</a>, Sisterson &amp; Co. LLP<br /> ?*Bring your own lunch<br /> <a href="https://cmu.ca1.qualtrics.com/jfe/form/SV_5d2h18LKYdKE6nH" target="_blank">Register</a></p> <p>Learn practical tax, accounting and business considerations that startups face in their first&nbsp;few years&nbsp;of operation.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <description><![CDATA[Speaker:†William RichardsonDate:†Tuesday, Jan 28 on 12:30 PM - 2:00 PMLocation:†Swartz Center for Entrepreneurship, Tepper QuadDetail:Tax, Business and Accounting Issues for Startups* Tuesday, January 28, 2020? 12:30 p.m. ? 2:00 p.m.? Swartz Center for Entrepreneurship, Tepper Quad ?Presenter: William Richardson, Carissa Habsburg & Megan Rechenberg, Sisterson & Co. LLP ?*Bring your own lunch Register Learn practical tax, accounting and business considerations that startups face in their first†few years†of operation.]]></description>
      <author>comet.paws</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Deep Learning and IoT introductory workshop - quick and easy workflows using MATLAB (Ph.D. Only)]]></title>
      <pubDate>Monday, Jan 20 2:13 PM -0500</pubDate>
      <link>http://halley.exp.sis.pitt.edu/comet/presentColloquium.do?col_id=18705</link>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<b>Speaker:</b>&nbsp;VIPRESH GANGWAL and SARAH MOHAMED<br/><b>Date:</b>&nbsp;Tuesday, Jan 28 on 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM<br/><b>Location:</b>&nbsp;Gates Hillman Centers, Reddy Conference Room 4405<br/><b>Detail:<b><h2>Deep Learning and IoT introductory workshop - quick and easy workflows using MATLAB</h2> <p>Let&#39;s get started with Deep Learning and the Internet of Things!&nbsp; We&#39;ll do hands-on exercises: you&#39;ll use a webcam and a neural network to recognize images, aggregate data, and run real-time IoT analytics. This workshop will introduce some workflows and guide you through a hands-on demonstration using simple tools. No prior experience is necessary!</p> <p><strong><em>Presenters:</em></strong><br /> <strong>Vipresh Gangwal,</strong> Manager, Engineering Development Group, MathWorks<br /> <strong>Sarah Mohamed</strong>, Software Engineer, Statistics and Machine Learning group, MathWorks (joining remotely)</p> <p><a href="https://events.beamery.com/mathworks/deep-learning-and-iot-introductory-workshop-quick-and-easy-workflows-using-matlab-c03edhj5">RSVP Requested.</a></p> <p><em>Refreshments will be served.</em></p> <p>?</p> <p><strong>Sarah Mohamed </strong>is a Software Engineer for Statistics and Machine Learning at MathWorks. In her development role, she has worked on features that deploy deep neural networks to hardware such as GPUs, and on tools that allow models to be shared among various deep learning frameworks. She has also worked as a customer-facing engineer, helping customers to investigate and overcome technical challenges in their applications. Sarah helped deliver the Deep Learning and IoT workshop in 2019 at WECode, the largest student-led computer science conference for women in the US, hosted by Harvard. She delivered the same workshop in March 2019 at TechTogether, Boston?s largest student-led hackathon for women and non-binary individuals.</p> <p><strong>Vipresh Gangwal</strong> is a Manager in the Engineering Development Group (EDG) at MathWorks. He has coached and mentored dozens of engineers and computer scientists working in fields including robotics, artificial intelligence, deep learning, compiler design, code generation, controls, etc. Being part of EDG, he has worked with customers from a variety of industries, many of who are technology leaders in their fields. &nbsp;He will leverage his own research experience working with robotics and neural networks, along with the insights he has gained from working with the customers and other engineers.</p> <p><em>(Since the successful debut at the Grace Hopper Celebration 2019, this workshop has been featured in many conferences) </em></p> <p><a href="http://www.cs.cmu.edu/career-center-events">SCS/ECE Careers</a></p> <p>For More Information, Please Contact:&nbsp;</p> <p><a href="mailto:careers@cs.cmu.edu">careers@cs.cmu.edu</a> / <a href="mailto:ece-careers@cmu.edu">ece-careers@cmu.edu</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <description><![CDATA[Speaker:†VIPRESH GANGWAL and SARAH MOHAMEDDate:†Tuesday, Jan 28 on 4:00 PM - 5:00 PMLocation:†Gates Hillman Centers, Reddy Conference Room 4405Detail:Deep Learning and IoT introductory workshop - quick and easy workflows using MATLAB Let's get started with Deep Learning and the Internet of Things!† We'll do hands-on exercises: you'll use a webcam and a neural network to recognize images, aggregate data, and run real-time IoT analytics. This workshop will introduce some workflows and guide you through a hands-on demonstration using simple tools. No prior experience is necessary! Presenters: Vipresh Gangwal, Manager, Engineering Development Group, MathWorks Sarah Mohamed, Software Engineer, Statistics and Machine Learning group, MathWorks (joining remotely) RSVP Requested. Refreshments will be served. ? Sarah Mohamed is a Software Engineer for Statistics and Machine Learning at MathWorks. In her development role, she has worked on features that deploy deep neural networks to hardware such as GPUs, and on tools that allow models to be shared among various deep learning frameworks. She has also worked as a customer-facing engineer, helping customers to investigate and overcome technical challenges in their applications. Sarah helped deliver the Deep Learning and IoT workshop in 2019 at WECode, the largest student-led computer science conference for women in the US, hosted by Harvard. She delivered the same workshop in March 2019 at TechTogether, Boston?s largest student-led hackathon for women and non-binary individuals. Vipresh Gangwal is a Manager in the Engineering Development Group (EDG) at MathWorks. He has coached and mentored dozens of engineers and computer scientists working in fields including robotics, artificial intelligence, deep learning, compiler design, code generation, controls, etc. Being part of EDG, he has worked with customers from a variety of industries, many of who are technology leaders in their fields. †He will leverage his own research experience working with robotics and neural networks, along with the insights he has gained from working with the customers and other engineers. (Since the successful debut at the Grace Hopper Celebration 2019, this workshop has been featured in many conferences) SCS/ECE Careers For More Information, Please Contact:† careers@cs.cmu.edu / ece-careers@cmu.edu]]></description>
      <author>comet.paws</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Demystifying Medicine - Taxol: Discovery, Mechanism and Cancer Treatment]]></title>
      <pubDate>Wednesday, Feb 12 11:19 AM -0500</pubDate>
      <link>http://halley.exp.sis.pitt.edu/comet/presentColloquium.do?col_id=18709</link>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<b>Speaker:</b>&nbsp;Jung-Min Lee<br/><b>Date:</b>&nbsp;Tuesday, Jan 28 on 4:00 PM - 5:00 PM<br/><b>Location:</b>&nbsp;Online - Webinar<br/><b>Detail:<b><p>The Demystifying Medicine Lecture Series is designed to help bridge the gap between advances in biology and their applications to major human diseases. The lectures include presentations of patients, pathology, diagnosis, and therapy in the context of major diseases and current research. All clinicians, trainees including fellows, medical students, Ph.D. students, and other healthcare and research professionals are welcome to attend.<br /> For more information go to <a href="https://demystifyingmedicine.od.nih.gov">https://demystifyingmedicine.od.nih.gov</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <description><![CDATA[Speaker:†Jung-Min LeeDate:†Tuesday, Jan 28 on 4:00 PM - 5:00 PMLocation:†Online - WebinarDetail:The Demystifying Medicine Lecture Series is designed to help bridge the gap between advances in biology and their applications to major human diseases. The lectures include presentations of patients, pathology, diagnosis, and therapy in the context of major diseases and current research. All clinicians, trainees including fellows, medical students, Ph.D. students, and other healthcare and research professionals are welcome to attend. For more information go to https://demystifyingmedicine.od.nih.gov]]></description>
      <author>comet.paws</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Immunotherapies for Progressive Multifocal Leukoencephalopathy]]></title>
      <pubDate>Wednesday, Jan 01 6:28 PM -0500</pubDate>
      <link>http://halley.exp.sis.pitt.edu/comet/presentColloquium.do?col_id=18617</link>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<b>Speaker:</b>&nbsp;Irene Cortese<br/><b>Date:</b>&nbsp;Wednesday, Jan 29 on 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM<br/><b>Location:</b>&nbsp;Online - Webinar<br/><b>Detail:<b><p>CC Grand Rounds: Immunotherapies for Progressive Multifocal Leukoencephalopathy<br /> For more information go to <a href="https://www.cc.nih.gov/about/news/grcurrent.html">https://www.cc.nih.gov/about/news/grcurrent.html</a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <description><![CDATA[Speaker:†Irene CorteseDate:†Wednesday, Jan 29 on 12:00 PM - 1:00 PMLocation:†Online - WebinarDetail:CC Grand Rounds: Immunotherapies for Progressive Multifocal Leukoencephalopathy For more information go to https://www.cc.nih.gov/about/news/grcurrent.html]]></description>
      <author>comet.paws</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Using Animals Responsibly in Biomedical Research]]></title>
      <pubDate>Wednesday, Jan 01 6:28 PM -0500</pubDate>
      <link>http://halley.exp.sis.pitt.edu/comet/presentColloquium.do?col_id=18619</link>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<b>Speaker:</b>&nbsp;Amy Cassano<br/><b>Date:</b>&nbsp;Wednesday, Jan 29 on 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM<br/><b>Location:</b>&nbsp;Forbes Tower, 7th floor, conference room 7039<br/><b>Detail:<b><p>The Clinical and Translational Science Institute&#39;s&nbsp;(CTSI) Responsible Conduct of Research (RCR) Center offers workshops as a resource for researchers and trainees. The RCR Center workshops are available to help you achieve your training goals and to support your research activities here at the University of Pittsburgh.</p> <p><strong>Responsible Use of Animals in Biomedical Research</strong>, presented by Amy Cassano, DVM, DACLAM, cVMA. Senior Executive Director of DLAR.</p> <p>This workshop discusses considerations and practical approaches to the responsible conduct of animal based biomedical research. Strategies to foster productive, collaborative working relationships and facilitate successful animal research at the University of Pittsburgh will be presented.</p> <p>This RCR workshop will take place at Forbes Tower, in conference room 7039.&nbsp;<strong><a href="https://ctsi.arlo.co/register?sgid=215b2448a0774e4b8c96162b1ef336a9">Click here</a> to register.</strong></p> <p>View the&nbsp;<a href="https://ctsi.pitt.edu/education-training/responsible-conduct-of-research-training/">RCR workshop schedule</a>&nbsp;for other opportunities.</p> <p>(Subject matter: animal subjects)</p> <p>&nbsp;</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <description><![CDATA[Speaker:†Amy CassanoDate:†Wednesday, Jan 29 on 12:00 PM - 1:00 PMLocation:†Forbes Tower, 7th floor, conference room 7039Detail:The Clinical and Translational Science Institute's†(CTSI) Responsible Conduct of Research (RCR) Center offers workshops as a resource for researchers and trainees. The RCR Center workshops are available to help you achieve your training goals and to support your research activities here at the University of Pittsburgh. Responsible Use of Animals in Biomedical Research, presented by Amy Cassano, DVM, DACLAM, cVMA. Senior Executive Director of DLAR. This workshop discusses considerations and practical approaches to the responsible conduct of animal based biomedical research. Strategies to foster productive, collaborative working relationships and facilitate successful animal research at the University of Pittsburgh will be presented. This RCR workshop will take place at Forbes Tower, in conference room 7039.†Click here to register. View the†RCR workshop schedule†for other opportunities. (Subject matter: animal subjects) †]]></description>
      <author>comet.paws</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Grand Rounds - Post-arrest prognostication: We can be better and faster]]></title>
      <pubDate>Sunday, Jan 26 5:57 PM -0500</pubDate>
      <link>http://halley.exp.sis.pitt.edu/comet/presentColloquium.do?col_id=18769</link>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<b>Speaker:</b>&nbsp;Jonathan Elmer<br/><b>Date:</b>&nbsp;Wednesday, Jan 29 on 12:00 PM - 1:00 PM<br/><b>Location:</b>&nbsp;Scaife Hall, 1105<br/><b>Detail:<b><p>Critical Care Medicine presents Grand Rounds presenter Jonathan Elmer, MD, MS from the Departments of Emergency Medicine, Critical Care Medicine, and Neurology</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <description><![CDATA[Speaker:†Jonathan ElmerDate:†Wednesday, Jan 29 on 12:00 PM - 1:00 PMLocation:†Scaife Hall, 1105Detail:Critical Care Medicine presents Grand Rounds presenter Jonathan Elmer, MD, MS from the Departments of Emergency Medicine, Critical Care Medicine, and Neurology]]></description>
      <author>comet.paws</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>